他请你吃的那么多晚餐
All those supper's you've had off him.
噢
Ouch!
你们对性的态度真守旧
You've such a Victorian attitude to sex, you two.
你父母不会就让你这么优哉游哉地走掉吧
Your parents wouldn't let you swan off like that, would they?
他还没跟他们说
Well, he haven't told them yet.
但大卫会编个什么故事出来的 他总是那样
But David will come up with some story, he usually does.
是啊 我发现了
Yeah, I've noticed that.
香奈儿香水 香奈儿香水
Chanel perfume, Chanel perfume.
香奈儿口红 香奈儿口红
Chanel lipstick, Chanel lipstick.
你在抽的这种奇怪的烟 寿百年
Those funny cigarettes you were smoking. Sobranies.
一人10包
Ten packets each.
那个香奈儿的香水多少钱?
How much is that Chanel perfume?
你是那个要去巴黎的女孩吗? 因为...
Are you the girl going to Paris or are you not? Because...